PERFECT CROWN
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS WERE FILMED SAFELY
Seong Huiju!
Come on out now.
Just give me a second!
Don't you find him to be so impatient?
Ah. He is generally of a most easygoing disposition.
We're late!
- Why that… - No, Your Ladyship!
My apologies.
Yes, please check the seat number for me.
Thank you.
Wait, is Ms. Seong still getting dressed?
She must be sewing the gown herself.
She could've made two by now.
Seong Huiju!
Well, at this rate…
PERFECT CROWN
EPISODE 6
Her Majesty said your attendance would not be required.
Uncle insisted I be there.
His Royal Highness did?
Yes.
Your Majesty.
You came.
How could I refuse a request from the Queen Mother?
Announcing Her Majesty the Queen Mother.
:cue
Thank you for inviting me, Your Majesty.
I would've been most delighted to have been invited to the reception too.
It is such a shame…
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
I hope you enjoy the banquet.
How would you find her as Grand Prince I-AN's consort?
She is neither too remarkable nor of too humble a station.
Is she not quite suitable?
Announcing Grand Prince I-AN.
It was a request from I-AN.
It seems he wishes to leave her a handsome parting gift.
We must honor his wishes.
So there is a use for this after all.
Don't you dance this often?
I hated these lessons the most.
Me too.
Even so,
this seems quite effective.
Everyone's eyes are on us.
You should only have eyes for me.
As if we were hopelessly in love.
I hear you, but this won't be enough.
I know. :cue
Follow my lead.
Wait, don't tell me that ring is…
Is that Queen UIHYEON's ring?
Gosh, she's so lucky.
Your Royal Highness.
Compared to you…
my pace may seem much slower.
Even so…
will you give me your hand in marriage?
Your Majesty.
Will you honor us
with your royal blessing?
Your Majesty.
You have my blessing.
I wish you great happiness, Uncle.
You too, Ms. Seong.
I am deeply honored, Your Majesty.
:cue
Prime Minister Min.
Utilize your veto power.
Your Majesty.
Royal marriages must be approved by the prime minister.
His Majesty approved it with everyone watching.
That is exactly why!
You are the only option we have.
The Crown and the Cabinet
must remain unified.
That's right.
Yes, of course. All right, then.
You must've had quite a day.
Oh. Aide Choi.
Is there usually no cell service here?
Ah. They probably blocked the signal today because of all the guests.
Ah. Then is there anywhere with a wired connection?
Wired connection…
Follow me.
Our sincerest congratulations, Your Royal Highness.
To you as well, Ms. Seong.
Who knew
you had such a gift for deception?
I meant what I said when we spoke earlier.
Though you may not believe me.
Did you think I would simply let this stand?
And if you do not?
Do you plan to go against His Majesty's royal command?
Do not be too enraged.
I simply wanted my marriage
to be conducted on my terms.
A grand prince's marriage is hardly a private matter.
How did someone so well-informed…
ever see fit
to amend my brother's will?
- That is absurd-- - Smile.
There are many eyes on us.
Jeongwoo.
Shall we? :cue
That ruthless brat never showed up?
Yeah, she's not in her room or the library either.
I thought the ninth graders had their exam today.
I guess she won't be the top laureate this time.
Maybe someone locked her up.
You think? But who would do that?
You never know.
She was always early, though.
ELEVATOR OUT OF ORDER
Hello?
Is anyone out there?
Damn it!
- There's someone in here! - Huiju?
Jeongwoo.
Take my hand.
Are you okay?
Come with me.
Where are we going?
- You tell them for me. - What?
Tell them I'm late because I was trapped in there.
They'll believe you.
Are you still against this marriage?
Can't you give me a break?
If I lose you, I'll have no one left.
Promise me.
That you'll never lie to me again.
Then I'll always be on your side.
Okay.
This is Queen UIHYEON's ring, right?
She always wore it.
I saw it when I was a kid, but I still remember it.
It was just so pretty.
But are you sure you can just give this to me?
It's your mother's ring.
Of course not.
That is a national treasure.
Return it when we get divorced.
Geez, just take it now.
They've already got plenty of shots of it.
Forget it.
Mother didn't even like that ring.
Why not?
Perhaps it was too heavy?
I guess you were her favorite.
This ring is a national treasure, after all. :cue
Yet she passed it down to you.
Not to your brother, the future king.
That decision left my father furious.
Father…
detested giving me anything.
That's fathers for you.
My goodness.
Could you be any prettier?
Do you like roses?
Pardon?
David Austin. Juliet roses.
These are Peony roses.
- They're all roses. - Huh?
My parents run a flower shop.
Ms. Do,
are you a flower shop heiress?
How's the response been?
They're going nuts out there.
Because of the proposal? Did foreign media pick it up?
- Both domestic and international media. - Ha.
KOREAN PRINCE'S PROPOSAL BREAKS CLASS BARRIER
I-AN PROPOSES TO SEONG HUIJU
Set up a meeting with the PR team tomorrow.
I already set it all up.
It's at 10:00 a.m. tomorrow.
Your Royal Highness, can I wear this ring to my interview tomorrow?
Do as you wish.
Look at it. Isn't it so pretty?
-  It's so pretty. - Look with your eyes, not your hands.
So pretty.
Wow, this is insane.
He proposed to her?
Babe, we're officially a royal family now!
I know, right?
So I'm officially Grand Prince I-AN's…
brother-in-law now.
That's right.
What's wrong?
Something doesn't feel right.
You just don't like the idea of Huiju becoming a royal, do you?
No, that's not it.
Babe, she needs to become a royal
for you to become the sole Castle Group heir.
I know that.
Then what?
About that damn mechanic who died.
Don't you think something feels off?
You have a point.
:cue
Announce me.
Your Majesty.
Lord INPYEONG has arrived.
Show him in.
Nuptials?
This is nonsense.
I will petition His Majesty to rescind his command.
You will do no such thing.
A royal command that can be overturned in the blink of an eye
is no command at all.
So?
Will you just accept it?
Grand Prince I-AN…
knows about the late King's dying wish.
You intend for Grand Prince I-AN to ascend the throne?
Have you truly gone mad?
It will be better than dying.
It would be better to die.
I'd rather see you dead.
For the sake of the Crown Prince.
It did not appear to be a remark made in passing.
- You were certain-- - I doubt he has any evidence.
The fire that day…
reduced everything to ashes.
Thus,
I shall accept
that unsavory union.
- Your Majesty. - As long as he knows about that will,
we can never join forces with him.
- So? - Seong Huiju.
She will prove to be his weakness.
It would be best to keep her within arm's reach.
Do you not agree?
A 21ST CENTURY CINDERELLA, COMMONER TO ROYALTY
I'm not entirely on board either, but what choice do we have?
He's right, Father.
There was a public proposal, and His Majesty gave them his blessing.
Oh, right.
Father, maybe we can take this chance to redistribute the company shares--
Dayeong.
Yes?
I need you to call your parents.
My parents?
We need to plant someone in the palace.
Your sister
should have at least one person she can rely on.
CASTLE BEAUTY
- By the way, Babe. - Yes?
I thought your father disliked Huiju.
He does dislike her, but he hates it more when others pick on her.
What?
That's just how he is.
I can't believe I'm seeing it in person.
How many carats is this?
Seriously? :cue
Well, anyway…
Have you named your successor yet?
My successor?
Royals can't work.
Then, you know, your company…
You'll need to hand over your management rights.
- So? - What do you mean, "So"?
I mean…
This company is your life's work.
This is when family steps up.
You wouldn't want to hand it over to a complete stranger…
Right?
- Don't you agree, babe? - Of course. Yes.
Your dear brother will take good--
That is my decision to make.
Did you find out what I asked about?
Talking to you is like talking to a brick wall.
Anyway…
…I did find him.
He went to great lengths to find him.
I know, right?
Listen, it was not easy at all. Nowadays…
Damn it.
She just won't let me talk.
He's dead.
What?
He died.
So I dug around a little, just in case,
but I found nothing.
No parents. No siblings.
Listen, you meet all kinds of crazy people in life.
- For… [bleep] …sake! - Damn, you scared me.
That… [bleep] …I should've killed him myself.
But some… [bleep] …asshole beat me to it!
I forgot who you were for a second there.
That's five minutes. You need to leave now.
- Us? - Yes.
Wow, our company nowadays is just… Nobody knows their place anymore.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Never again.
Telling me to leave? I'm a Senior Managing Director, you know.
My apologies.
Take care.
This is the list of anticipated questions. Take a look.
Okay.
Why are these questions so cliché?
"The Grand Prince's strengths and weaknesses?"
Who would even care?
It should be more like…
"When was your first kiss?"
"Who wins in a fight behind closed doors?"
Aren't these the sort of questions they should be asking?
The palace already screened them, so they had no other choice.
Ah.
I swear, they really need a new PR team.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
How did you two meet?
Our first meeting?
Mmm…
It was quite a long time ago.
We went to the same school.
Were you just strictly classmates back then?
No romantic feelings?
And Your Royal Highness? You are here too, are you not?
Will you receive demerit points as well?
Sparks flew back then as well.
But nothing ever happened between us back then.
It just felt like…
we came from two very different worlds.
From when you were just acquaintances to now,
what would you say is the biggest change?
Hmm…
Being overprotective?
Seong Huiju!
She will be staying here for the time being. :cue
I am trying to protect you!
He must think that I'd break at the lightest touch.
As if I were made of glass.
"Glass."
Why? Do I seem unbreakable to you?
Just kidding.
Your Royal Highness.
Why don't you take a break and look at this?
What is it?
This is the draft of Ms. Seong's interview.
A CHAT WITH SEONG HUIJU, CEO OF CASTLE BEAUTY
Steward Kim, Her Ladyship is here!
Goodness me!
Your Ladyship!
You act like it's been years.
I know, right?
At this rate, another lovers' quarrel will be the death of me.
As if you didn't snatch the hopae from my hands.
Why is Ms. Do here?
She's my right-hand woman.
Let's go inside.
Yes, ma'am.
What?
I asked for those files ages ago and yet…
Wow.
Let me call you back.
Do you like it?
Oh… It's just so pretty.
You can go now. I'll take care of the rest.
No, it'll only take a second…
Very well. Please let me know if you need anything.
Return to my private residence.
What?
Am I someone who shows up and leaves on your command?
We'll start packing immediately.
Ms. Do.
I'm worried about leaving you alone.
At least you'll be safe there with the Royal Guard.
- Right? - Of course.
Our Royal Guard is top-notch.
One more thing.
Please go ahead, Your Royal Highness.
There's a spy at my private residence.
A spy?
Is it someone on your staff?
Do you have a name?
Just a moment.
PERSONAL DETAILS REPORT LEE AREUM
Oh?
Any chance of wiretaps or hidden cameras?
That's impossible.
Both the palace and private residence are checked regularly.
Then that means she only reports what she can see and hear.
How many times have I told you to just kick her out?
She'll only be replaced by someone else.
I'll move in with you.
You will?
Yes.
Would that be okay?
As you wish. :cue
Ms. Do, I need to take this.
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
The palace, tomorrow?
We need to plan the wedding.
I'll have a car sent for you.
Don't drive yourself.
Huiju.
Jeongwoo!
But are you going to help us plan the wedding too?
You didn't think I would?
I'm the prime minister, and your wedding is basically a state affair.
That's true.
Your Royal Highness, Ms. Seong has arrived.
Prime Minister Min is here as well.
Show them in.
Did the two of you…
come here together?
No.
We met at the palace gates.
I see.
Now then,
shall we get started?
Can we push back the meeting a bit?
Yeah. Around two hours?
- This is taking longer than expected. - Ms. Do!
Okay, thank you.
You must be here with Ms. Seong.
- Yes. - I see.
Did you see the flowers on the way in?
The palace becomes a flower paradise this time of year.
- Especially… - Hmm?
- Ms. Do? - Yes?
The lilies and hydrangeas are especially magnificent.
If you're free later…
Hydrangeas?
See you.
Your royal wedding will be held on a scale comparable to the Crown Prince's.
For what reason?
The royal family has seen many tragedies.
The people suffered just as much.
Thus, we must take this chance
to remind the public that the Crown still stands strong.
- That will-- - Make the Crown more useful.
Both at home and abroad.
That's right.
There are notable economic benefits too.
Royal weddings generate more revenue than they cost, after all. :cue
How much does it cost?
Around…
So hot!
Are you okay? Did you burn your tongue?
No, I'm fine.
Wait, hold on.
What kind of revenue could justify that cost?
Prime Minister Min.
Seong Huiju will soon become my wife.
Please mind your conduct.
You do not need to keep up appearances with me.
Oh…
You see…
Jeongwoo knows everything.
Until your divorce is finalized without incident…
I will do my best to assist you both.
Yay!
Your father seemed pleased, didn't he?
Of course.
Who would ever be against their in-laws securing royal ties?
Wait, that's why he was pleased?
Not because I'm going to inherit Castle Group?
We can't be sure of that just yet.
What?
Wait, what's that supposed to mean?
Han Dayeong.
What's that brat doing here?
- Uh, hello. - Babe, shoulders back.
Here to see your parents?
Yeah, my father wanted to give my sister-in-law a wedding gift.
I assume you saw the news?
I thought you weren't close to your sister.
Well, you know, family can be…
What are you talking about? They're basically inseparable.
Uh, yes, we're close.
- Really? - She also leans on me so much.
I'm wondering if I should join her in the palace.
- You? - You?
Yeah.
It's not like she has a mother to lean on.
I have to step in. What choice do I have?
She has no other choice…
I swear I had no choice. He walked in when I was talking to Ms. Do--
You call that an excuse?
That's just what happened.
I'm sorry.
But it's not all so bad, is it?
- What? - We need the approval
of the royal family and the Cabinet for every little thing.
With Jeongwoo on our side,
we don't need to worry about the Cabinet anymore.
How are you so sure?
- What? - About Prime Minister Min.
How can you be sure he'll always take our side?
Because, obviously…
That's a bit too naïve, no?
Excuse me?
A businesswoman should know better than to trust people so easily, no?
:cue
Your Royal Highness and I only started getting in sync.
Then it would make more sense for me to trust him over you, no?
He's always been on my side since we were kids.
- What? - Let's face it.
For all I know, you could just bail out on me again.
Calling you fickle would be an understatement.
"Fi… Fickle"?
Just know that I really want to draw up a contract,
but I'm doing my best to hold back.
Draw it up.
- What? - Draw it up.
- Draw it up? - Draw it up.
Let's draw it up!
So we will divorce…
Within three years at the latest.
The sooner, the better.
- Post-divorce asset division? - Aside from the clothes on your back,
any real estate or assets bestowed by virtue of royal status
must be relinquished.
Might as well fight over pennies.
"Pennies"?
Very well, then.
However, I will not be relinquishing my title or rank.
The privileges attached to them shall also be maintained.
- For life. - As long as you do not cause
public controversy or violate the law, you shall retain them.
There's more.
One.
All matters concerning the palace shall remain confidential,
during the marriage and thereafter.
Two.
All matters between us shall remain confidential,
during the marriage and thereafter.
- Three. - All matters shall
remain confidential.
I hear you.
- In turn, Your Royal Highness-- - If secrecy proves difficult,
just forget it happened.
It's all pretend anyway.
It won't matter.
Your Royal Highness, the Queen Mother has arrived.
Your Royal Highness.
Escort her in.
Your Majesty.
I am Huiju of the Seong Family.
I stopped by after hearing you were both here.
I wanted to ask if you two would join me for dinner.
We are soon to be family, after all.
:cue
- Enjoy. - You too.
Will Ms. Seong be okay? What if she gets indigestion?
She'll be fine. She has an iron stomach.
No, you see…
The Queen Mother can be…
a bit old-school. She can be super intense.
It's fine.
Ms. Seong is quite the rebel too.
I see.
So stop worrying and eat already.
Our bosses will be on edge after their dinner.
All right then.
Truth be told, I was worried they might really fall for one another.
I mean, come on. Who wouldn't fall for Our Royal Highness?
With that face and figure, and those shoulders like…
Nothing to worry about.
Ms. Seong likes trophy men.
What did you say?
Trophy men.
Ones that show up and leave on command.
Spineless men.
So just eat your food.
The chances of a man who's summoned people his whole life
and a woman who's bossed people around her whole life
falling for each other are basically nil.
- What about you, Ms. Hyejeong? - What?
What's your type?
They really know how to cook their wild greens here.
Kudos, Auntie.
I do hope the food is to your taste.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
This liquor is made from pears.
It is quite strong.
Ah.
Queen Mother.
She…
Can you not handle your alcohol?
I certainly can.
Wait, were you really scolded that much?
He wrote letters of apology so frequently.
I am sure there were enough to make a whole book.
Is that so?
I guess you were quite the troublemaker.
Drink some water.
Hold on. You're blushing.
You're totally blushing.
Your face is red.
If His Majesty, your father, had still been with us…
I wonder what he would have said about this union.
Queen Mother.
He would have requested a letter of apology.
He so frequently scolded you for standing in your brother's way.
Surely, he would not have approved of you standing in your nephew's way.
You should stop there.
Can you truly claim to be wholly innocent
in the death of the late King?
What goes through your mind when you look at His Majesty?
Do you wish to stand in his way
and eliminate him, just as you did the late King?
Are you okay? :cue
Do you know why he was given
the royal title of "I-AN"?
"I" as in "rule."
"AN" as in "peace."
It calls upon him to refrain
from harming the stability of the Crown.
Please excuse us now.
It will soon be time to close the palace gates.
Slow down.
I said, slow down.
Just know I'm holding back because we're not married yet.
You keep saying you're holding back.
If I had it my way, the Queen Mother would be pulverized--
Whoa!
Just hang in there.
As soon as we're married,
I will clear everything that stands in your way.
You don't believe me?
I do.
So get me out of here.
What?
I don't want to sleep here tonight.
Should you be driving right now?
Leaving the palace was defiance in itself.
Aren't you scared?
The accident wasn't too long ago.
I like driving.
It feels like flying.
And I can go fast.
I'm not allowed to run or ride a bike.
But I'm allowed to drive.
I don't understand the logic.
Do you want to fly for real?
Do you intend to propose to me?
You've watched way too many dramas.
Then why are we here?
Did you rent this?
It's mine.
So what? You want me to fly here?
You obviously can't fly here.
We can fly right over there.
Wait here.
Seong Huiju. :cue
You should not run, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
I dried these myself, Ms. Do.
How is it?
- It's nice. - I knew it!
I don't offer this to just anyone.
But I had some yesterday.
- Don't you have work to do? - Mmm.
Uncle!
- Your Majesty. - Oh, Your Majesty.
Oh, uh, is it just you here?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Where is Uncle?
I heard Ms. Seong was here as well.
Oh, we are also wondering where they could be--
You can just tell me, Your Majesty.
I will be sure to pass along any message.
No need.
- Your Majesty. - A mighty sigh from His Majesty…
Your Majesty, what is the matter?
He's so cute.
Is someone chasing you?
Why is no one here?
I asked them to clear out.
Can I get you anything?
"A royal can only eat in verified restaurants."
Wh-- What are you doing?
Just do whatever you want today.
- What? - I told you it's just us here.
- But a royal-- - Royals never marry commoners.
So why are you marrying me?
My goodness.
Are you okay?
- Who gets seasick on a yacht? - It's just indigestion.
It's indigestion.
I mean, I could prick your finger for you.
- What? - There should be a needle somewhere.
- A royal… - Are you scared?
Because a prick would hurt so much? Shaking in your boots?
Fine. Let's do it.
Are you sure this works? Not just a placebo effect?
Ouch!
I feel all better now.
How did I ever put my trust in such a cowardly prince?
"Cowardly"?
I am…
just not familiar with home remedies.
Let's go now.
Go on.
I told you I'd let you experience flying.
- Come on. - Wha-- :cue
Oh!
This is too dangerous. Come down now.
Here.
Hold me tight.
You said you'd let me fly.
Why are you the one flying?
Let's switch. I can hold you.
- Forget it. - Why not? Come on…
Your Royal Highness.
Are you hurt anywhere?
You said I can do whatever I want.
:cue
EPILOGUE
You'll be attending the second half, right?
Probably.
I assume you can waltz?
Can you?
I am a top laureate through and through.
Let's not do that.
Hold me up like this.
Here I come.
PERFECT CROWN
We were just caught up in the moment.
I mean, it's not like I threw myself at him.
Why did I do that?
Not for me.
I didn't do it just because I was caught up in the moment.
I did it because it's you.
Don't you think it's excessive? Maybe they're falling for each other.
I mean, they actually look like they just started dating.
Something bothering you? You've been acting strange.
You're being unnecessarily sweet to me.
I shall wait.
Until the day you can no longer restrain yourself.
Restraint always followed desire.
But it's not easy this time.
By chance, do you have feelings for me?
Translated by Justin S. Kim
PERFECT CROWN